Hello friends, if you are a customer of AAA Bank
and you want to do eKYC in AAA Bank, that is, you
want to update KYC online, then how can you do it? If you
want to know, then stay tuned, in this video
we are going to talk about this topic till the end.
Hello friends, I am
Pran and welcome to you. You have
come to G Life iMobile app, I have opened it,
as soon as it opens, enter the six digit MPIN here and
login to your account. See, if you
need to update KYC, then the bank will
send you such a link, you login in it,
from here
you can directly go by clicking on Proceed to KYC,
otherwise you go to your dashboard,
here the Services option is visible,
click there, after clicking there you will
see, there are many options on it,
scroll down a little,
you will see Update KYC Public
Profile, click on it, as soon as you
click on Update KYC Profile, the
first option will appear here, Update
KYC, click on it, like that
Click above, your customer ID will be
visible here, account number will be visible,
first select the customer ID, then
click on proceed to update KYC,
right now you are being asked for location here,
allow it at this time and it
will redirect you to this page, your customer
ID, account number etc. are visible here,
your PAN number, email address etc. are
also visible, so here we
will click on proceed to KYC, as soon as you
click on it, you will come to this page
where you will be asked to enter your Aadhaar number,
enter the Aadhaar number
and here
click on the box 'I have read and understood', as soon as you
click on it,
a page will appear here,
read it, then agree, now
click on generate OTP,
after clicking on generate OTP, there is an OTP
which will go to the mobile number linked with your Aadhaar,
enter that OTP here and verify OTP, after doing the
verify OTP, here your Aadhaar
and bank details will be displayed.  It will
confirm the details like whether your Aadhaar number
given in the bank is the same or not, that
check will be yes, then your name
with Aadhaar, whether
both are correct or not, such check will be yes, date
of birth check will be yes, the
address written on the Aadhaar is also visible here,
scroll down the page a little, you
can see here, the
assisting address which is currently in your account will be
visible here and below one thing is being asked do you want to
change your
communication address, do you want to change your address, do you want to
remain the same as the one already given, then we do
not have to change it below, if we want to change then
click on yes, if we do not want to change then
we will click on no
and the box which is visible below I have
by declare will click on it and
click on proceed to F ATCA details, right now in this page you are being
asked for residential details, current
residential status will be Indian, country of birth
India, all will be India only  Here the country
of citizenship will be this, here one more question is being asked are
you US citizen, we
will select no here, then click on I understand this
box and click on proceed to
profile details,
now in profile details you will have to select your
occupation, sub occupation,
education, your gross annual income, all this
here, so you
select all that here and after this
click on I have read and understood this box, as you click on it,
then again some terms and conditions will
appear, read it, then I agree,
then click on confirm details,
now see, whatever details
you have already filled, everything will be
visible here, you check it once,
then go on proceed for e-sign, as soon as you go on it, it will
redirect you to another website, here
if you want to sign this online then
click on the box in front of by clicking this check box
and click on proceed now  As you
click on proceed, your
form for this sign will be filled with all the details
here. You
can check it once here and then proceed.
Now the terms and conditions will appear. Now
your consent will be taken once again by
clicking this check box. So, click on the
box in front of it and
click on accept and sign. Now
you will be asked again to enter your Aadhaar number here
and after entering the Aadhaar number,
we will click on send OP here.
See, we have entered the Aadhaar number
and send OTP. Now while
sending OTP, an OTP will go to our
mobile number which is linked with Aadhaar.
That OTP has to be entered here. We have
entered the OTP. The box below is I am the
holder
Aadhaar number. Click on this box and
click on perform e-sign. As soon as you
click on perform e-sign, all
your details which you have been filling in for so long will be visible on this page.
You can check all this by scrolling down
and  You submit it, while submitting,
congratulations,
you have submitted your details successfully, your details have been submitted successfully,
your request has been submitted successfully,
after some time you will
also get a confirmation message that your request has been
accepted and your eKYC has been
accepted, friends, in this way
if you want to do eKYC in III Bank online,
want to fill your KYC details, want to update them, you can do it
easily, I hope
friends, you liked this video, you must have come to
know about how you can do eKYC in III Bank, how you can update it, if you liked this video,
like the video and do
not forget to subscribe to the channel, we will meet again
in the next video with a new topic, till then
friends, please allow me, hello